Guide to the Daily Worker and Daily World Cartoon Collection GRAPHICS.024.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Ephemera and other Graphics, 1953-1992
  Series IV: Ephemera and other Graphics contains non-cartoon graphics and ephemera found in the collection. The material ranges in date from 1953-1992. Of particular interest are posters from a Camp Unity Reunion dance, anti-Reagan newsprint posters and fliers from the Daily World, and a synthetic printing plate from the Worker for the issue regarding the execution of Julius and Ethel Rosenberg. The material ranges in format and includes art prints, fliers, posters, and pre-press works.
  - Camp Unity Reunion Dance: Poster (3 copies), undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Colon, Jesus: Flier, undated (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Daily World: Fliers and Posters (anti-Reagan) (newsprint), 1984 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Greek Art Prints, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - International Longshoremen's Association: N.J. Docker (logo), undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - International Union of Students: Poster, undated (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Oktober Klub DDR: Flier, undated (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Political Affairs: Covers (pre-press), 1992, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Rosenbergs: Cover of The Worker (sythentic printing plate), 1953 (Box 12, Folder 9)